Visit turkision.com for more!
You'll go and protect the tax
gold we collected for the emperor.
This map shows the areas
that soldiers will camp.
Be quick.
They must have reached Karasu by now.
What about Osman?
-What about him, sir?
-Osman...
...is just a wounded prey.
He'll never make it out of this forest.
Hit the road. Go.
While you're supposed to
send your dogs after me,
...where are they going now?
I'll burn this headquarter down over you.
But first I need to find out...
...what this important task is, Constantin.
Husrev.
Husrev?
Husrev. Husrev? What
happened to you? Who did this?
The dog called Kanyumaz.
He's clearly up to something here.
-But I don't know what it is.
-He must have come...
...to tell Constantin that I serve Osman Bey.
What are you talking about, Holofira Hatun?
Constantin got a letter...
...from supposedly Elcim Hatun.
Mehmed Bey is playing a trick against us.
The snake called Andra confessed
everything before she died.
You finally got what you deserved, Snake.
Soldiers!
This traitor has turned out
to be serving Osman Bey.
She tried to kill me.
I'll find a horse for you
to get out of Bursa safely.
-Can you ride to the tribe?
-For sure.
You aren't safe here anymore.
Why don't you come with me?
Don't worry.
I'll be safe here.
Constantin will try to use me before killing me.
Besides, I haven't completed my duty here yet.
I can't go back without punishing the ones
who played a part in my father's murder.
We don't have much time.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
That's Osman.
He's found us.
-Osman...
Yes, Osman.
-Where are you going, Aleksios?
-This is just a fool's bravery.
You're on your own and wounded.
Wind can only take dust from the rock.
Attack!
Now you'll speak.
You worked with Ulcay.
You killed Gunduz Bey together. But tell me.
How did you dare to confront me?
I got orders from Constantin and did it.
Just like your alps.
-Spare my life.
-Cut it! Constantin have no power to do that.
Tell me. Who supports you?
Emperor. He knows you want Bursa.
He made an agreement
with Olcaytu to protect Bursa.
You can never achieve! You
can't beat them, Osman Bey.
They are too powerful.
More powerful than Allah's army?
Now it's your turn.
And Olcaytu will be the next.
This note you took from Constantin.
What is in the other locations
apart from Bursa and Yalakova?
-I don't know.
-Don't you know where you were going?
I can skin you alive here.
-Speak!
-Alright. Alright.
We're sending the war taxes to the emperor.
And the emperor will recruit
an army with the gold, huh?
Yes. He'll have an unprecedented army.
-Spare my life.
-You know what?
I can still hear Gunduz Bey's screams.
So...
An eye for an eye.
The day will be over shortly but we
couldn't find any trails from my Bey.
We can't trace in the dark, my Shahzade.
We have to use the daylight as long as we can.
-Trails here!
-Demirboga! Check it out.
The trails belong to Bursa
horses. Also some footprints here.
-It seems they searched here.
-Come on, Cerkutay Bey.
Show your skills.
Lion is wounded but
still alive, thanks to Allah!
Don't be upset, my Shahzade.
Holofira on one hand and my Bey on the other.
How can I be not upset?
My Shahzade, that dog...
...won't kill Holofira Hatun until he's
done with her. He wants to use her.
The dog called Constantin is going to die.
So Holofira will be saved, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
And Elcim Hatun will be acquitted.
My Shahzade.
They got on the horses here and went north.
Alps, come on
Nobody but us knew that
Holofira was a spy in Bursa.
Right?
No, mother. Nobody but us knows this secret.
But Constantin knows.
We'll find out how he learned that.
Someone hostile to us
would only expose this secret.
You're right, Gonca. But...
How could they learn
while only we knew about it?
If you talked about it somewhere
someone may have heard.
But you wouldn't talk about
such an important matter in public.
Right?
Holofira is risking her life for Osman Bey.
She's a spy in Bursa.
No, mother. Even I wouldn't mention it anywhere.
This secret didn't put only
Holofira but also my father in danger.
Only someone hostile to us would do this.
You mean my brother?
How could he know, Alaaddin?
Alaaddin, we can't be sure about anything.
There is nobody but Mehmed
who would expose this secret.
-But he doesn't know.
-What if he found out?
How could he have learned it?
I...
...might have done this.
Near Constantin Headquarters
Who are you?
Ulgen is right. When Gonca fell sick..
-..we talked about Holofira issue.
-However, there was no one around.
How can you do such a mistake?
-Elcim?
-We were not paying attention, Bala Hatun.
-We made a mistake.
-That day..
..Mehmed came right after you.
Alaeddin? Are you sure?
I remember.
How can I forget that day.
He acted soft as well.
You were there too, mother. I am telling you..
..Mehmed did it.
-However, we can not be sure.
-Yes, we can not.
How will we find out?
If he has the heart, he
will tell the truth to my face.
-Alaeddin?
-Alaeddin, stop.
Evil in the day is better than
goodness in the night, son.
He threatened my father's life, mother.
-Will he get away with that?
-Alaeddin.
Even if my brother did
this he will not tell you.
I know how to make him talk.
My son. Now is not the time.
Not the time, wait for morning at least. He
is still at Frontier Marketplace anyways.
Hasan!
My Shahzade.
Have them watch Mehmed.
If he leaves Frontier Marketplace..
..catch him and put him in the caged tent.
-Inform me as well.
-As you command, my Shahzade.
I want to say that Grand Emperor..
..I've defeated Osman..
..who has defeated many Lords..
..many commanders.
I am honored to tell you that I took Gunduz..
..and his trusted Beys..
.and Osman is looking for a place to escape.
Now it is time to eradicate all Turks.
The taxes I've collected is on its way.
It will be loaded into ships
and reach Constantinople.
Then, you will assemble a..
..grand army for me to eradicate Turks.
I will kill them in their sleep.
What happened to the guard?
Holofira is at Bursa as well.
What if she is, Elcim?
Don't you know we are going to Bursa for duty?
To keep the promise I've given you..
..and ease the pain in
your heart, even a little bit.
Do not ever..
..question my loyalty. Ever.
My Allah..
..free me from this trouble.
My Shahzade's troubles are very
big. Storms going on inside him.
He couldn't have predicted Elcim
Hatun doing something like this.
You are right, Cerkutay.
Elcim Hatun is of Kayi heritage.
She knows traditions. She
wouldn't do such a mistake.
Someone who knew what is happening
between Elcim Hatun and him did this.
It is dark as well. No sign of my Bey.
What is he doing, how is
he, we don't know anything.
My Bey is like a mountain. He
got the smell of Konstantin it seems.
It seems he won't be back before beheading him.
-He is wounded, Boran.
-So, brother?
His wound gives him strength.
A valiant wanders around with a bandage.
He is alone against a whole army.
May Allah allows us to
find him without any trouble.
Everyone can go to the war with alps.
The real bravery is going alone.
That is what it means to be Osman Bey.
We will have some infidels too right?
Ten thousand soldiers will walk from the west.
They will take Lefke and Bilecik from them.
Fifteen thousand soldiers from south.
They will take Kestel and Inegol..
..from their hands first.
Then, the armies will merge.
They will eradicate all tribes..
..and Yenisehir, as well as all Turks.
You won't escape from me, Osman.
You both will destroy them..
..and also tell them the
location of the war, is that so?
-Osman is here!
-Osman?
Alone?
You came for your death, Osman.
Are you running away, Osman?
-What is this explosion?
-It seems my father found their location.
Come on, alps!
I will be back Osman!
Of course you run. Go ahead.
I know where you are going.
However, you won't escape from me.
Iltutan!
Many tribes who are left in the darkness..
..saw Osman as salvation and followed him.
They even reached to Yalikova borders.
However..
..soon they will see that they are wrong.
They already did, father.
No one knows if Osman is alive or not.
-They are scared.
-Good.
Germiyanids will relieve them, Mehmed.
The tribes who stand with Osman..
..all of them will see.
How will we do that father?
Osman is alone.
There is no way for him
to get out of this trouble.
Let him get what he deserves first..
..you will see after.
You keep your eyes on Kayis.
-Are we allowed, my Bey?
-Come in, Kanyumaz.
Any news from Osman?
He is still missing, my Bey.
If you get into matters
that are bigger than you..
..you are bound to drown, they say.
He is in a tough situation.
One other thing, my Bey.
What is it, Kanyumaz?
Karesi Bey.
He is still with Osman Bey.
They say he even saved him from the ambush.
So he is still with Osman.
Since you insist on your mistake..
..then you will be..
..history like Osman, Karesi Bey.
Karesi Bey followed Osman..
..and stood against Germiyanids.
Tomorrow, I will go to Kutahya.
Both Osman and Karesi Bey will pay for this.
You will also finish your
duties and come by my side.
However, you will learn..
..what happened to Osman first.
If Osman is dead, he is saved.
If he is alive..
..the things I will do to him..
..will be worse than death.
So you are on your way to get the gold, huh?
I will show you. Come on!
Husrev!
-My Allah!
Come here.
Are you alright?
Bring some water! Come on!
Alright, Husrev.
They found out that he was a spy. Is he alright?
They don't believe Holofira.
They say Elcim Hatun... Elcim Hatun did this...
They played a game against her.
So that this game was exposed,
why didn't Holofira come here?
Constantine is her cousin...
He wants to use Holofira to catch Osman Bey.
May Allah help her. Husrev...
Could you find the traitor? Who is it?
Tell us.
Kanyumaz...
Mehmed sent him to Bursa.
Mehmed... I knew it! I knew he
would make a treacherous move!
Alps! Take him to the healing tent!
Come on..
What did you do, brother?
I will not let you get
away with this, Mehmed!
Alaeddin!
Let me go! -Stop...
How can I stop, mother?!
-How can I stop, mother?!
We trusted him, but he
lured us into a trap, huh?
But now it's over! It's over!
Mother... mother... If Alaeddin goes there
with this furor, he will kill my brother!
My Allah, protect him!
Hasan... Prepare the Alps. You will
go after Alaeddin once he leaves. Go.
Yes Bala Hatun.
Alaeddin! Alaeddin!
Alaeddin! Stop!
Don't go like this! Please!
Just wait for a moment! -My Gonca...
Don't, my rose! Don't stand in
my way! You cannot do this now.
Alaeddin, I am not asking you to stay.
I swear. But just don't go with this furor.
Wait for a moment. Look...
Terrible things will happen if you go
there with this anger. Stop Alaeddin!
My father, my brother,
Holofira.. They are all in danger!
Because of whom? Because of
Mehmed who was blinded by his anger!
But I know how to open those blind eyes.
Come on! -Alaeddin! Alaeddin!
My Allah, protect my baby!
In the name of Allah... Come on!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Damn horse..
I am almost there... Hang on, Constantine.
You will live for your revenge.
Look at this horse...
Look at this horse..
You see, right? There is no
other horse like you, Iltutan!
You have no rivals.
Constantine... Where are you going to go?
Now your end has come.
So you went this way. Let's go!
What happened here?
A fire must have broke out.
Apparently they have seen hell before dying.
It seems as if a Gokboru and its
pack have come here, brothers.
The only pack and Gokboru is my father.
Osman Bey has dived into
the midst of the infidels alone.
Allah Allah! IIIAIIah!
Not only did my Bey enter the infidels' nest...
...but he also cut them into pieces.
Alps! We will search everywhere!
We will try to find Osman Bey's tracks! Come on!
Orhan Bey! There is a letter here!
Kayi dagger...
My father left this. He
wanted to show us the way.
He wants us to go after him.
The places between Yalikova
and Bursa are marked, my Bey.
Everyone died. Constantine's
dead body is not around.
So that dog is still alive.
There are tracks!
Orhan Bey... It leads to north.
Dog Constantine is still
alive. My Bey is after him.
The route we will follow is on the paper!
Inform Karesi Bey and Alps! Come on, Alps!
Where are you running, Constantine?
I told you that the truth
was at the tip of my sword.
Now you will meet the truth.
I couldn't have found a...
...more beautiful place to kill you, Osman.
Let's see. Let's see.
So you are running away, huh? So
you are running away, Constantine.
Run away then. Run away.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
-Both Mehmed and Kanyumaz are
at the marketplace, my Shahzade.
Be careful. Don't let them escape.
Come on. Come on!
Mehmet! Where are you Mehmet?
Come here! Mehmet!
Mehmet, come here!
Kanyumaz... You traitor dog..
Come here... Come here..
You traitor dog... Do you think
you can run away from me, huh?
I am innocent! VAIIahi I am innocent!
-Alaeddin!
You are a sold dog...
Forgive me Alaeddin Bey! Forgive me!
I am innocent!
You wanted to spread evilness in my tribe, huh?
You tried to kill my father!
-Alaeddin!
You worked with infidels, huh?
Stand up! You will tell me everything! Stand up!
Alaeddin!
-You will tell me everything!
Alaeddin...
Now it is time to leave Gokmen.
Prepare our horses.
-Yes my Shahzade.
Speak! Speak! Where is Mehmed?
Where is the man who holds your leash?
I don't know!
-You don't know, huh?
You don't know...
You don't know.
Tell me! Tell me! Who gave that letter to you?
Who informed you? Tell
me! Or I will kill you here!
I just... I just obeyed the orders.
Mehmed Bey gave me the letter.
And I took it to Constantine.
I have no other guilt!
That was not your only
mistake. You betrayed us twice.
Take this dog away! I still have
things to do with him! Take him!
Gonca... Why did you come here?
Why, Alaeddin?
My Shahzade... Mehmed Bey is running away.
Mehmet!
Where will you go, huh? Where will you go?
-Alaeddin!
My father, my brother,
Holofira... He tried to kill them all.
He will pay for this, Gonca.
Mehmet!
-My Allah, let me be strong.
Come on! -Come on!
You went after a prey bigger than your throat.
Now you will lose your life.
Our prey is always big. But...
...we never hunt alone. We never eat alone.
We don't do anything for ourselves.
-Samil!
We do everything for our
tribe and for our people.
What about you?
Don't worry... I will
not eat you alone.
If you finished your sentence, I
am ending your story here, Osman.
As the headquarters burnt...
...wolves saw the fire. My story has just begun.
We've arrived, my Bey!
Constantine..
Good... Your son has come.
Now I will enjoy killing you here.
Constantine... We have..
...just as many men behind you
Shamil!
This battlefield won't be a grave
for Turks but you, Constantin.
Osman Bey's wolves arrived in time to fight.
Alps!
Attack!
Come here, you heathen kind!
You will get your share...
...from Solgur Agha's wrath today.
This is our land out battlefield.
You will only get death today.
Today, you're going to die!
Look at me.
You... Stand up.
You brought the trouble to my land.
Get up!
You killed Gunduz Bey who I called brother.
Get up! Up! You killed my alps.
They became martyrs because of you.
Just wait. Wait.
In these lands, justice can
only be served under my flag.
I provide justice! Here...
The warriors you see here
are fighting all around...
...to provide justice!
And you've been waiting to
die under my sword for long.
This is the time.
You dog!
-You can't even take your life anymore.
-Get your head up.
Get your head up.
I'll kill you.
And you will tell...
...your people in hell...
...that you couldn't beat Osman Bey yet.
I have avenged our brothers and kept my promise!
-Thank Allah!
Thank Allah!
Why did you attempt to do such
a thing on your own, Osman Bey?
I knew you'd arrive in time. Thank you.
Samil arrived just in time,
my Bey. He made us stronger.
Well... If we had attacked all together,
...they might have had a
chance to take the gold away.
But now all our people will share the booty!
If the gold coins had arrived in Constantinople
they'd come back as swords against us.
Exactly. Exactly.
Will the gold fit into our
treasure room, my Bey?
Well,brother...
Have you ever seen Osman Bey
put the booty into the treasure room?
Can we finish this booty
by handing out, my Bey?
We will hand it out. We will.
These gold coins will
strengthen our nation and state.
These are the coins that were
taken from Bursa people by force.
We'll use the gold to save
them from the oppression.
People didn't only get
oppressed in Bursa, my Bey.
But some caused unrest and
Holofira got exposed as well.
And they made it look like Elcim Hatun did it.
Here, my Bey.
-Take this.
-Thank you, thank you, son.
Thank you.
But Elcim would never do this.
As long as this dog lies down
here, Holofira will be at ease.
We've completely settled the matter.
Thank you, my Bey... Well...
I'll go to Bursa and take
Holofira if you let me.
She isn't safe there anymore.
-Well...
Don't act carelessly just
because we cut off this dog's head.
As you order, my Bey.
Solgur Agha, go ahead to the tribe.
We'll come later with the gold.
-Tell alps to escort us on the way.
-As you order, my Bey.
I'll protect you at the cost of my life.
Thank you.
-Samil.
-My Bey.
Well done. Thank you.
Thank you. You and your
warriors did a great job.
You proved yourselves.
You and your warriors will
watch the western borders.
This is your new duty.
Thank you, my Bey. I won't disappoint you.
My Bey, what about these dead bodies?
Samil and his alps will take them away.
They'll be eaten by the animals.
-Come on, alps. Come on.
-As you order, my Bey.
Here we go, alps! Our
Bey trust us for the borders!
It's an honor to protect the border.
It's more important than our lives.
-May Allah help us! -Aameen.
Brother! Brother!
Brother! Brother?
Brother, brother!
Brother! Brother!
-Gokmen?
Alaaddin!
Alaaddin...
Mehmed, Mehmed...
-Alaaddin.
You never fight bravely, do you?
You either run off or beat
people by tying them up.
You can't teach me how to be brave, coward.
-Come here.
-Aladdin, don't.
You are the coward, Mehmed!
Is this how your return the helping hand?
You sold us out to the heathens.
You disgraced your sister!
-Alaaddin, stop.
-You deserved that, Alaaddin.
You deserved it!
-Well...
-Brother!
-This is the end, Mehmed.
I told myself to stop for Gonca's sake.
-Please stop this.
-But you never stopped and cooled down.
I won't stop either now. I won't stop!
Please stop!
Please don't do this.
Alaaddin!
You started this war.
You've come here to kill me...
...but I will take your life, Alaaddin.
And I'll take my sister away.
Gonca will stay with her husband. But...
-You're going into the grave.
-Alaaddin.
Alaaddin!
Gonca? Gonca! Let's go, my dear.
Gokmen! Gokmen!
Gonca! What did you do Gonca!
Gonca! I did everything for my State!
The day will come when I will take
back my sister and our lands from you!
I will ease the pain of my father!
Gonca!
My Gonca, are you alright?
Alaeddin, he was
not the brother I knew.
He sold us. Alaeddin he sold us to the infidels!
-Stay calm.
-I have no one left!
Alaeddin I have no one
left! I don't have a family!
-I have no one! -That's not true.
You have me. Don't worry.
Don't worry, Gonca.
Alaeddin. What did you do, brother?
-Be cautious.
-As you command, my Shahzade.
-Orhan?
-Holofira.
The fate of this wound..
..is to always bleed it seems, Lord's Daughter.
Thank you.
Is Osman Bey alright?
Konstantin set him up.
My father got out alive from that dog's trap.
However, Konstantin..
..Konstantin understood the
wrath of Osman Bey, Holofira.
-What do you mean?
-Holofira.
We've avenged your father,
and all those oppressed people.
We’ve avenged your father,
Konstantin is dead.
You didn't need to come. You
could've sent word with alps.
We did our duty, Holofira.
I came to take you away from here.
Take me away? To where?
My father wanted you to be somewhere safer.
If you do not want to stay in our tribe..
..we can settle you in one of the cities.
Everyone who knew my
connection with you is dead.
I am safe now, Orhan Bey.
My duties here hasn't ended as well.
Konstantin may be dead, however, his father..
..my uncle is still alive.
I will track him down.
I will go to Constantinople if needed.
I will only live for my vengeance from now on.
However, no matter where I am..
..my service to Osman Bey will continue.
Thank you.
If you say so.
Since you don't want to come..
..of course I will not object.
Don't object, Orhan.
Do not.
Remember when you told me
that destiny brought me to you?
The same destiny set us apart.
You will go back to your home..
..to your hatun.
You will be very happy.
And I will be very happy after that.
Your smile..
..may your smile never goes away, Holofira.
Even though I won't see you..
..I hope that you be always happy.
Go now.
Go.
Come on.
Come on, go now.
Goodbye.
I am welcomed.
May you live long, Osman Bey!
-My Bey, are you alright?
-I am alright, Bala.
-Father.
-My Fatma, I am alright.
Elcim, we avenged your father.
We sent that dog Konstantin to hell.
-May you prosper.
-May you prosper, Osman Bey. Thank Allah.
However, I can not see Orhan Bey. Is he alright?
He went to Holofira.
As you know, his secret is revealed.
Thanks to him, I was saved from slander.
We took the heads of those who stood against us.
We made infidels bow down with our swords.
We brought their treasures to our tribe.
With Allah's permission victory became ours.
Of course it did.
While we have our Allah..
..they can not oppress us.
Now, we want to use this treasure..
..for the conquest of Bursa. People!
-Do you allow?
-We allow!
-We allow, Osman Bey!
Thank you.
From now on, everyone will know..
..that we are just starting our conquests.
Long live Osman Bey!
My Bey. Let us tend to your wounds.
I am alright.
Leave me be with my cousin.
May you burn well, Konstantin.
You killed my father..
..for nothing.
You sent him to death..
..while he was innocent.
And your book is closed now.
Now, it is time..
..for your father.
I will make you meet in hell.
Just wait.
You scared me this time, my Osman.
May Allah protects you.
Bala. You missed me a lot it seems.
Did I wake you up?
My beautiful.
Tell me.
Why are you watching me sleep?
I was scared, my Osman.
I was very scared.
I couldn't show it, however..
..I had to stand firm.
Just wait.
What scares you, tell me.
My Hatun is not scared of anything easily.
I am not scared of enemies or infidels.
I am afraid of losing you.
Afraid of missing a lot, my Osman.
Come here.
Don't be scared.
You are my sunshine.
You light my way.
Your prayers will protect me.
Do not worry.
So that's why you are going to the enemy alone?
I was not alone.
What is this wound?
Look here. While you have so many more.
And you are asking about a scratch?
It's nothing. Happened at the training.
I was not paying attention
as I was busy missing you.
You know what?
Even this little scar...
...disappears in my heart.
Well... When I fight the enemy,
...they think I'm on my own.
But none of them knows.
None of them.
You are... You are in my heart.
I take strength from you,
my family and my dreams.
But none of them knows this. Well...
GERMIYANOGULLARI BEYLIC
KUTAHYA
Osman Bey completely got out of control.
He crossed the line.
The more powerful he became
the more arrogant he got.
Did he take permission from us? No.
Now his presence...
...compromises our power.
Listen to me carefully now.
-Father.
Mehmed... Mehmed
juos Aw
Mehmed, what happened to you?
-Who did this?
-Kayis...
Kayis attempted to kill me, father.
Why did they do that?
They believed a woman's
words and slandered me, father.
They killed Gokmen.
They took Kanyumaz captive.
Who? Which of them?
-Alaaddin.
Alaaddin, father.
Bring the healers!
Now there's blood feud between us.
They killed...
...my warriors and alps.
I know what to do.
Now Osman's land is a place of raid for us!
Prepare the raiders immediately!
We're going to raid Osman's lands!
I will ruin..
...your sleep in the bed
What are you waiting for? Go!
Mehmed, my son... Hang on, son.
Mehmed... Hold on, son.
Healers!
Allah has spoken the truth.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
My Gonca.
May Allah accept your prayer, my Bey.
Thank you, my hatun. May
Allah be pleased with you.
The milk is now warm. You can drink it.
Are you even mothering me now?
Fine. I'll drink.
Does the wound that my brother opened...
...hurt?
Do not upset yourself, my Hatun.
You are not guilty.
My Gonca.
From now on, it will be even more difficult.
This is called war, my rose.
I want something difficult
from you, I know, but...
..from now on, you should be stronger.
Don't worry, my Bey.
It's over now.
I made sure of it today. From now on...
...there will be only us.
When will we organize our wedding, Coy Hatun?
The weather is nice as well.
What should we do? Should we hold our wedding?
If you tell me no again..
...we will be the first ones to hold a
wedding with their baby in Kayi tribe.
No... We can't do that, right? We can't.
What should we do?
Let's just do it, huh? But...
...so that we've waited this long...
...I am expecting a legendary
wedding, Alaeddin Bey.
Allah Allah..
You Trickster Hatun...
I would never say no if you
asked for a beautiful wedding.
That is your duty, Alaeddin.
I said what I needed to say.
Then...
...I will organize a glorious wedding for you.
Good.
My baby... I and your
mother will have a wedding.
Osman Bey... I am writing this letter
to inform you about a great danger.
You avenged my father and the oppressed.
Constantine got lost, but...
...this made Emperor
Andronikos even more furious.
I found out that he will
send a new Lord to Bursa.
I know the Lord that will come here.
Constantine's father, my uncle...
...Justinianus Paleologos.
He is a ruthless and vile man...
...who killed his own brother...
...my father. He is coming
to protect Bursa and...
...and to take his revenge from you.
Thanks to Allah. Thank you, Hatun.
Did you... believe that I exposed Holofira?
I won't lie to you, Hatun.
I was suspicious at the beginning.
But even then, I remembered how...
...brave and glorious Hatun you were...
...and that you only lived for
our Beylics, not for yourself.
Then I said "Elcim Hatun would never do this."
"My Hatun would never do this.", I said.
Thanks to Allah. My innocence is proven...
How is Holofira? You are
the last person who saw her...
Elcim...
I am not complaining.
You did well by
saying goodbye to her.
I owe Holofira again.
Thanks to her, my innocence was
proven. That's why I am curious.
Is she alright? -She is.
She will now live in the
monastery. That's what she decided.
Now we left everything in the past.
Everyone will live their own lives.
But those left behind...
My father now rests in peace.
Thanks to you, my Bey. Thanks to all of you.
You took my father's revenge.
I promised you, Hatun. Thanks to my Allah...
...He granted me with keeping my promise.
It is my duty to make the pain that...
...hurts your heart disappear.
Because you and I..
We are family, Elcim.
Even if it's just the two of
us for now, we are family.
It's not just the two of us now, Orhan Bey.
Elcim?
I am pregnant, my Bey.
You are going to be a father.
What are you saying, Hatun?
This is such blessed news!
Thanks to Allah!
Thanks to Allah, Elcim.
You made me so happy...
Attention! Osman Bey!
We are ready, my Bey.
You may sit.
I am...
...the owner of all lands at the frontiers...
...the protector of Turks...
...the guardian of Islam..
..and the servant of Allah..
...Osman Bey.
GERMIYANOGULLARI BEYLIC
KUTAHYA
I am the one who has
grown my Beylic every day...
...which was attempted
to be destroyed by fitna...
...into a state.
I have made Iznik kneel. I have
made commanders bow down.
What I expect...
...from the man who receives this letter is
to recognize the state I have established.
Otherwise, within the borders of
my lands, he will not be recognized...
...and his all properties
will be destroyed. Whoever...
...opposes the blessed state of the Turks...
...may they express their opposition
not with a letter but on the battlefield.
May they stand before us. May
the blessings of Allah be upon you.
Those letters will be sent everywhere!
First, it will be sent to Emperor
Andronikos in Constantinople.
It will be sent to Yakup
Bey in Kutahya, Candar...
...Karesi Beylics, Kinez' in north...
..Badawis in south.
They will be sent everywhere.
And they will all recognize...
..our state.
Here.
The messengers can set out.
Orhan Bey.
-Did you send the messengers for scholars?
-Yes my Bey.
We sent messengers everywhere
and invited them all to our lands.
We told them that we will do everything
necessary to benefit from their knowledge.
Thank you, thank you. We will use
all of our opportunities for them.
Our land will be the homeland
of knowledge and wisdom.
-I hope so, my Bey.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Samil.
My Bey, we sent Alps everywhere in west.
Alps communicate with each other
from a distance with burning arrows.
If they attack, they will
all go there and fight back.
Everywhere in our lands is safe, my Bey.
We should not worry about this.
Our enemies must worry about this.
Now... we will organize our wedding.
Come on.
My Bala... I told you that you
couldn't ride faster than me.
What is that, my Osman? You speak as if you won.
e came here at the same time.
-That's why I am surprised.
You became a grandmother,
but you can still compete with me.
Why would you say that?
Alright, alright. That was a joke.
So... the seeds we planted...
...they all turned green and bear fruit now.
-I cannot describe how happy I am.
-I am also so happy, my Osman.
The things we dreamt of in the
past are now becoming true, huh?
Right... right. We are
going to have grandchildren.
Our family is growing, our lands are expanding.
Like the roots of this mighty sycamore...
...our state will also be strong.
Thanks to your faith and strength, my Osman.
You are the root of this state.
The stronger the roots,
the stronger the body, right?
Our children are following your path too.
All of us. My Bala.
If I am the roots of this mighty sycamore...
...you are the soil from which those roots grow.
I draw my strength from this soil.
You nurture us with your compassion and mercy.
I have given my life and
heart to this dream, my Osman.
Your path is my path.
I know. I know. How will I ever repay you? How?
You have shed...
...many tears, blood, and sweat for this da'wah.
You... you are my companion on this path.
The mother of my children and...
...the Sultan of my heart.
-Is that so?
So where do we go now, Osman Bey?
-Our way...
...is the way to the state.
What...
Give me strength, Allah...
Mother.. It smells amazing.
It is Toyga soup.
If someone sees your face, they will think
I am starving you. Why are you drooling?
Go! Go! You are just like your father.
Ghazi Alp. This is Herise.
Taste it.
It looks really good. Allah Allah...
Huseyin Agha... where did you come from?
I came from Sogut, my
valiant. I am the cook of Sogut.
When the lamb is cooked,
we can say the meal is ready.
Praise be, master.
Praise be. These necks must be delicious.
Mother... Don't
get jealous, but...
..he cooks better than you
Don't act like you never ate that thing!
O, people!
The steppe is awakening..
...those who are brave shoulder
the burdens. The brave lead the way...
...the elders follow from behind.
Clear the path! The hennaed goats...
...are coming on shoulders!
-May men be tested...
...may valiants show their talents! Come on now!
Let's see who is the fastest in the tribe!
My Bey is talking about me,
brother. Give up while you still can.
This time I won't let you pass me.
-We'll see who will pass...
...and who will win, Alaeddin.
-Let's go, brother.
Come on, take the goats.
-Let's go.
-In the name of Allah.
Cerkutay! -My Bey!
-Shoot the arrow!
Yes my Bey. In the name of Allah.
-Start!
-Come on!
Come on!
Orhan!
No! Come on, no stopping!
Come on! In the name of Allah.
You used to race while I wait back then,
now our sons race and the hatuns wait.
Our sons got married
and brought joy to our tribe.
They did.
Come on valiants!
Come on, my Bey!
Praise be, praise be!
So, Hatun.
Now there is no doubt..
..that your valiant is the
fastest in the tribe, right brother?
You think you got past me now.
I let you take the lead. Or, you know..
..you can't beat me if I had two lambs on me.
-So you say so.
-Yes.
Look, Gonca Hatun is saying something.
Run, Orhan Bey!
They are still kids, Bala.
They are. They never grow old.
People!
There will be a feast!
Today is the happiest day
of the tribe! Come on valiants!
Long live Osman Bey!
Mother, look at this wattle!
Look at this, praise be!
-Look here!
-I see it!
Praise be, cook!
Mother, what were you feeding me all this time?
Gazi, from now on..
-..you will eat the ladle!
-Stop, mother!
Praise be, Master Huseyin.
You let your craft speak again.
May you prosper.
Enjoy, my Bey.
Thank you.
In the name of Allah.
Praise be. It is delicious.
Time goes on.
-Come on now, Boran.
-My Bey.
Play your qopuz...
..in this joyful day.
Sure, my Bey.
Alps shall equip weapon.
The flag shall rise up to the sky.
The dress shall be stained with blood.
Bursa is in our heart.
Even if 40 enemies unite...
Even if they spread 40 unrests...
Even if the way is long...
Bursa is in our heart.
Even if 40 enemies unite...
Even if they spread 40 unrests...
Even if the way is long...
Bursa is in our heart.
Take us away...
Do not stop, go on you!
Grown like a plane tree.
Bursa is in our heart.
Even if 40 enemies unite...
Even if they spread 40 unrests...
Even if the way is long...
Bursa is in our heart.
Even if 40 enemies unite...
Even if they spread 40 unrests...
Even if the way is long...
Bursa is in our heart.
-Well sung, Boran.
-Thank you, my Bey.
We have Bursa in our hearts...
Elcim.
I'm sorry for what happened.
We almost blamed you because of my brother.
It's not your fault, Gonca.
You forgive me.
I broke your heart, said bad things.
It's not a problem anymore.
It's just gone.
Praise be.
Praise be to my beautiful girls.
This is what being a family means.
Sometimes we get cross but we also make peace.
-May Allah not ruin our peace and order.
-I hope so.
I hope so, mother.
Nobody...
Nobody can pick the house they are born into.
But we can pick our family.
Of course we can, my beautiful girl.
-You're so beautiful.
-Thanks.
Yes, praise be!
I don't have any other families but you.
Here is the henna.
Mother.
Take a seat.
-Is this a joke? -Come on.
Well... I think... Everything must be complete.
There must be henna before the wedding.
Well... I'm the bride side today.
Prepare the gold, girl.
-I've prepared everything.
-Fine. Fine.
Bring it. In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Well... The bride isn't opening her hand.
Fatma, be a good sister-in-law.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
the merciful, the compassionate. Praise be!
Give it to me, girl.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks.
Come on! Let's apply henna.
Praise be to the bride.
Look at the bride!
Her hands have henna!
Don't say anything bad to
her or she'll go back home.
Her door is hennaed.
She has the nature of an angel.
May your henna be blessed, bride.
May your tent be sweet.
Look at the bride! Her hands have henna!
Don't say anything bad to
her or she'll go back home.
Her door is hennaed.
She has the nature of an angel.
May your henna be blessed, bride.
May your tent be sweet.
GERMIYANOGULLARl BEYLIC
KUTAHYA
You took my daughter from me.
You killed my warriors and alps.
You did this to my son.
And now you've even sent me a letter...
...saying you have become a state?
Now I have nothing else
but my wrath like this fire...
...to give you, Osman.
The door cannot be opened, Tall Shahzade.
You say it can't?
-Ghazi... Come on, boy.
-No! No!
-Come on. Hey, what are you doing?
This is between Tall Shahzade and me!
-Stay out of this.
-Cerkutay, stop.
Ulgen Hatun, Ghazi Alp is right.
Brother, you should open the
pouch before the door is opened.
Ghazi...
You know how it works.
Here.
Wow! You pay only this much for Gonca Hatun?
Fine, take this.
Gonca Hatun is mine. And
the coins are yours, huh?
You need to pay more, my Shahzade!
-Hey, stop this!
-Leave me.
-My Allah!
-Leave me!
-Who do you take after? Your mother?
My Gonca.
Well... Congratulations.
Here we go.
Praise be, praise be, praise be!
We thank Allah for letting us see this day.
Son.
May Allah give you a good fortune.
May Allah never let you have a defeat.
-Aameen!
-Thank you, my Bey.
Now you aren't a stranger...
...but a daughter to us, Gonca.
Feel at home here.
May Allah give you a long life, mother.
Well...
May Allah give you strength and peace at home.
May Allah give you
children you'll be proud of.
Aameen!
Amen, my Bey.
-My girl, congratulations.
-Thanks, Osman Bey.
My brother, may it be blessed.
Thank you, brother.
My Bey, with your permission,
...we'd like to give great news on such a day.
What is it?
If Allah permits, from now on, we'll
be more in numbers for our cause.
I'll have a baby to carry our
flag and swing a sword!
Praise be! Praise be!
If it's a boy, my Bey, with Allah's will
...we'll name him after his
grandfather Suleyman Shah.
-Praise be!
-Praise be.
On such a happy day you are giving me...
...the great news of two grandchildren, huh?
Let me kiss your hand, my Bey.
-Thank you, son.
-Congratulations.
-My Bey, congratulations.
-Thank you, Osman Bey.
May Allah give you a healthy baby, my girl.
-Thank you, mother Bala.
-May Allah give us a child..
...worthy of our nation and state.
-May it be blessed, I hope.
-Thank you, brother.
My Bey, may Allah give you...
...and your family long lives.
May Allah let your kin...
...prevail forever!
-Aameen!
-So be it!
Thank you, Solgur Agha. Thank you.
Well...
O people! Spread the news all around the world!
I want to see the valiants whose
hearts beat with us, ready for battle...
.after Friday prayer, in the unity square.
Let's show the strength
and might of our state...
...to everyone.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
If Allah permits, my Bey. If Allah permits, my Bey.
What did my Alaeddin Bey do?
He built a tent in the sky.
What did he do to..
...make Gonca Hatun happy?
He turned a horse into a stallion, a
cow into a camel and a sheep into a ram.
Did he break hearts? Did he say something bad?
He neither broke hearts nor said anything bad...
He married Gonca Hatun!
Then may Allah let them be happy!
Aameen!
May you be happy, may
you grow a family together!
Don't open your eyes, my Hatun.
Alaeddin, why did you cover my eyes?
I said don't open your eyes, Hatun.
-I did not.
You did not open your eyes, right? -I did not.
You can open your eyes now.
Alaeddin...
Alaeddin what did you do?
-Did you like it?
It looks beautiful!
Our love started with a daisy, right my rose?
I hope that from now on..
..we will..
...happily live in peace like
these daisies, right my Hatun?
With our children, if Allah permits my Bey.
If Allah permits.
My Gonca... -My Alaeddin...
The messenger of Allah
kept walking on his way...
...since his first revelation to...
...his farewell sermon.
And you are following the Sunnah.
You faced numerous obstacles...
...but you did not give up. You
confronted enemies in your path...
..and you defeated them.
However, know that your
way will be more difficult now.
As you approach your target, the
number of your enemies will increase.
It's not the visible ones but the hidden ones...
That's the actual difficulty, Sultan
of words. And the thing in me...
Only Allah knows it best.
When I am about to set out for a war...
...I sometimes ask myself...
..."Am I doing this for my nafs or...
...for the sake of Allah's consent?"
What does your heart say?
My inner self remains silent.
But saying it in front of
you will embarrass me...
...since it might be seen as arrogance.
Then tell me.
-Are you shooting the arrow?
-Never!
I would never say such a thing.
How dare I?
I repent. How dare I?!
"When you shot the arrow...
...It was not you...
But He was Allah who shot it."
(Surah Al-Anfal 17)
My Allah..
My Allah... My Allah...
Thanks to You.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
When The State of Seljuks fell..
..Turks did not have a State! So we said..
..if there is a greater one,
if there is a more fair one..
..let him come.
If we do not follow him, we are shameless!
Time and destiny showed
us that, to become a State..
..there is no other that
deserves being a State but us!
Thank Allah!
I went to a hundred wars!
I got alive from all of them!
I spent my life on the cause of holy war!
I witness that there is no other
that deserves being a State but you!
It's either the State or nothing!
The army of Turks! May you prosper!
May you prosper!
The thing that is State..
..will now be called "Osman".
My Beys, my alps, my bacis!
We've sent word to the whole World!
With Allah's permission,
everyone will recognize our State!
-We hope so, my Bey!
-However, don't forget!
State requires unity!
State does not accept seperation!
That is why we will be..
..like an enclosed fist! We
will live under a single banner..
..for the State of Turks!
Allah is the greatest!
-Orhan Bey!
-Yes, my Bey!
You will settle in Karacahisar..
..with my daughter Elcim
And you will prevent all attacks
coming from Germiyanids.
From now on, borders..
..will be under your control.
Thank you, my Bey.
-Son.
-Honored to..
..fulfill this duty, my Bey.
Come on then.
-Alaeddin!
-My Beyl
Our tribe will be under your control..
..with my daughter Gonca.
You will take care of our traditions.
As you command, my Bey.
And we will not give up..
..marching towards the
enemy, just like the first days.
Only Allah knows if we will be victorious.
Our intentions are not
victory, but the cause itself.
We will walk!
So that The Grand State of Turks live forever!
-Allah is the greatest!
I am Osman Bey.
I inherited the value from
my father Ertugrul Gazi.
I've made the whole World hear the cause.
I made the tribe I got from my father bigger.
I've established a State that
will be a shadow for Turks forever.
I've walked my way true.
I never disobeyed tradiitons.
I never disobeyed Qur'an.
I never did what Allah was against.
My advice to those after me..
..do not ever leave traditions.
My sons.
My alps. My scholars and my people.
May they never leave justice.
May you prevail walking the way of Allah.
So that..
...you may deserve the
tortures your ancestors endured.
Visit turkision.com for more!